we're moving
into space.
Even data centers,
we think, Elon
data centers,
leading that charge,
will start moving
start moving
into space, and
into space,
we won't have
the "not in
my backyard" and
my backyard"
the bureaucracy
associated
with data centers.
There's going to
data centers.
be huge job
creation around
the space exploration
and all of
space exploration
the opportunities
out there.
And then the
other one, and
other one,
you'll find this
you'll find
in our digital
assets section of
assets section
Big Ideas, is
the digital world.
Immutable private
property rights. Mm-hmm.
property rights.
We know from
economic history, the
economic history,
best way to
lift people
and countries
out of poverty
is with private
of poverty
property rights
that are immutable.
Well, that is
now moving into
now moving
the digital world
for the first
digital world
time, thanks to
blockchain technology.